http://www.ukelectronics.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Our Services
UK Electronics provides a comprehensive Electronic Equipment and PCB Design, prototyping, manufacture, and assembly of
either the PCB itself or the customers finished product.
Latest News
What would the world be like if PCBs didn’t exist?
Posted 28/09/2020
UK Electronics is the trading name of UK Electronics Limited, a private limited company registered in England, registration number 1753503. This privacy notice explains how we, UK Electronics, use any personal information we collect about you. How do we collect information about you? We collect information about you when you sell products / services to […]
Read more
Privacy Policy
Home Privacy Policy
UK Electronics is the trading name of UK Electronics Limited, a private limited company registered in England, registration number 1753503. This privacy notice explains how we, UK Electronics, use any personal information we collect about you.
How do we collect information about you?
We collect information about you when you sell products / services to us or buy products / services from us.
We also collect information when you visit our website, voluntarily complete surveys, voluntarily request our newsletters, provide feedback, apply for career opportunities and participate in competitions.
Website usage information is collected using cookies. To learn more about the use on cookies for website tracking please see our Cookie Policy.
How will we use the information about you?
We collect information about you to process your order, manage your account, maintain warranty records, and if you agree, to email you regarding other services that we think may be of interest to you.
UK Electronics will not sell or rent your personal data to third parties. We will not share your information with third parties for marketing purposes. We will share your information with third parties only for the purposes of completing tasks and providing services to you on our behalf. When this is done only the most relevant information is shared to complete the task and those third parties are bound to maintain security and confidentiality and not to share, sell or hire personal information.
In processing your order, we may send your details to, and also use information from, credit reference agencies and fraud prevention agencies.
Marketing
We would like to send you information about product and services of ours that may be of interest to you.
If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date. You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving your information to other members of the UK Electronics team.
If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please email marketing@ukelectronics.co.uk telling us this.
Access to your information and correction
Retention periods for this information are reviewed on a regular basis to ensure we do not store any information unnecessarily. As a matter of course, we store information for as long as we feel is suitable to maintain an acceptable level of service to our customers or until we are asked to delete it.
You have the right to request a copy of the personal information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all your personal information, please email marketing@ukelectronics.co.uk requesting this.
We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.
Website Cookies
Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavioral information. This information is stored for a limited time and is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.
For further information please visit: www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org.
You can set your browser to disable cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases some of our website features may not function as a result.
Other Websites
Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to our website so when you link to other websites you should read their privacy policies.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on our website. This privacy policy was last updated on 17 May 2018.
How to Contact Us
Please contact us if you have any questions regarding our privacy policy or information we hold about you by emailing marketing@ukelectronics.co.uk.
Contact UK:E
0161 626 4117
sales@ukelectronics.co.uk
Latest News
What would the world be like if PCBs didn’t exist?
PCBs have been described as one of the top 10 tech inventions of 20th century – so what would the…
Read moreView all news
Latest News
What would the world be like if PCBs didn’t exist?
PCBs have been described as one of the top 10 tech inventions of 20th century – so what would the…
UK Electronics is committed to providing high quality products, effective project management and outstanding customer service.
UK:E on Twitter
Tweets by UKEHQ
Contact UK:E
Schofield House, Lion Mill Yard, Fitton Street, Royton, Lancashire, OL2 5JX
0161 626 4117
sales@ukelectronics.co.uk
Copyright 2020 UK:E
